[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which of the following is a renewable resource?",
      "options": [
        "Coal",
        "Petroleum",
        "Solar Energy",
        "Natural Gas"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which resource takes millions of years to form and cannot be replenished?",
      "options": [
        "Wind Energy",
        "Forests",
        "Coal",
        "Hydropower"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What type of resource is water when used in the hydrological cycle?",
      "options": [
        "Renewable",
        "Non-Renewable",
        "Cyclic",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of a cyclic resource?",
      "options": [
        "Gold",
        "Water",
        "Coal",
        "Natural Gas"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which renewable resource is generated using wind turbines?",
      "options": [
        "Solar Energy",
        "Hydropower",
        "Geothermal Energy",
        "Wind Energy"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which non-renewable resource is used in nuclear power plants?",
      "options": [
        "Coal",
        "Uranium",
        "Natural Gas",
        "Iron"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Why are non-renewable resources considered unsustainable?",
      "options": [
        "They are expensive to use",
        "They take millions of years to form and cannot be replenished",
        "They are not used by industries",
        "They cannot be extracted"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a non-renewable resource?",
      "options": [
        "Coal",
        "Petroleum",
        "Wind Energy",
        "Natural Gas"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following metals can be recycled and reused?",
      "options": [
        "Aluminum",
        "Coal",
        "Natural Gas",
        "Petroleum"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "How can we conserve non-renewable resources?",
      "options": [
        "By using them excessively",
        "By replacing them with renewable resources",
        "By ignoring recycling techniques",
        "By using more fossil fuels"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    }
]
  